even though we thought that the
a pesar de que pensábamos que el tema de
Michelo issue was no longer giving more of itself
michelo ya no daba más de sí
recently there has been some
recientemente han habido algunas
news in the last few days that I wanted to
noticias en los últimos días que quería
update with you and that is that
actualizar con ustedes y es que han
some new things have happened to address
pasado algunas cosas nuevas que abordar
with you about these characters from
con ustedes sobre estos personajes desde
the fact that some have already been
el hecho de que algunos ya fueron
forgotten by the regime until
olvidados por parte del régimen hasta
now they simply want to wash their
que ahora se quieren simplemente lavar
hands as if they had done nothing
las manos como si no Hubieran hecho nada
before everyone saw Michelo as
antes todo el mundo veía a michelo como
a simple idiot for defending the
un simple idiota Por defender a la
dictatorship of Venezuela but with the passage
dictadura de Venezuela pero con el paso
of time more and more people
del tiempo más y más gente se fue dando
realized that he is a nefarious and
cuenta de que es una persona nefasta y
very dark person who whitewashed the worst
muy oscura que blanqueo los peores
crimes of the regime maduro himself
crímenes del régimen el propio maduro le
pays him to be his official propagandist and
paga para ser su propagandista oficial e
even abused his power to make
incluso abuso de su poder para
a woman disappear and if that were
desaparecer a una mujer y por si fuera
not enough Michelo laughed at everything they
poco michelo se rió de todo lo que
said that he deserved to go to jail for his
decían que merecía ir preso por sus
crimes but now he receives a complaint from
crímenes pero ahora recibe una denuncia
an International Court and it
por parte de una Corte Internacional y
is very likely that he will be arrested What's up
es muy probable que sea detenido Qué
my kids welcome one
pasa mi chavalería bienvenidos un día
more day to my channel I am Javi Oliveira if you didn't
más a mi canal Soy Javi oliveira si no
know me and you came across this video by
me conocías y ha llegado a este vídeo de
chance here on this channel we deal with
casualidad aquí en este canal tratamos
all the topics  virals of the moment and we
todos los temas virales del momento y
review all the news always
repasamos toda la actualidad siempre
trying to entertain you if you
intentando también entreteneros si te
like and are interested in this type of
gusta y te interesa este tipo de
content I invite you to subscribe it
contenido te invito a que te suscribas
is completely free activate the
que es completamente gratuito activa la
bell So as not to miss anything before
campanita Para no perderte nada antes de
starting with a complete update
comenzar con toda una actualización
on the subject of Michelo it is important to
sobre el tema de michelo es importante
emphasize something that recently happened
recalcar algo que recientemente ocurrió
and that was quite talked about and has
y que fue bastante comentado y tiene
some people outraged about it And that
indignada algunas personas al respecto Y
is that recently a
es que hace poco se hizo viral una
photograph of Maduro and an official
fotografía de maduro y un funcionario
sent by Donald Trump for
enviado por Donald Trump para misiones
special missions went viral named Richard Grenel whose
especiales llamado Richard grenel el
mission was to announce the
cual tenía como misión poder anunciar la
release of six
liberación de seis hombres
American men who were imprisoned in
estadounidenses que estaban presos en
Venezuela Grenel's visit surprised
Venezuela la visita de grenel sorprendió
many Venezuelans who expected
a muchos venezolanos que esperaban que
Trump to continue the maximum
Trump continuase la campaña de máxima
pressure campaign that he carried out against Maduro
presión que llevó a cabo contra maduro
during his first term however
durante su primer mandato sin embargo
possibly the cooling off on the part
posiblemente el enfriamiento por parte
of María Corina Machado and the
de María Corina Machado y el mundo
González world has caused the United States to
González haya hecho que Estados Unidos
lower the intensity a bit with
bajara un poco la intensidad con
Venezuela and it is with this context that we
Venezuela y es con este contexto donde
enter with Michelo evidently as it
entramos con michelo evidentemente como
could not be otherwise he did not take long to
no podía ser de otro modo no tardó en
make a video laughing at the right
hacer un vídeo riéndose de la derecha
assuming that Maduro had
asumiendo que maduro tenía en su misión
all the leaders of  the right
a todos los líderes de la derecha
simply because of the treatment in this so much
simplemente por el trato en esta
that they called it dictatorship dictatorship There it
tanto que decían dictadura dictadura Ahí
is Look Trump is going to negotiate with
está Mirá Trump va a negociar con
Nicolás Maduro today he sent his emissary
Nicolás Maduro hoy mandó a su emisario
gr what will the right say friend they are going to
gr qué dirá la derecha amigo les va a
burn what a taming Nicolás
arder tremenda domada le ha dado Nicolás
Maduro has given to all the squalid right wing of the world there he has it Trump kissing his feet and the worst thing is that this old man asked for the Venezuelans to be deported to other countries like Guantanamo or El Salvador Venezuelan who lives in the United States can you imagine he is imprisoned in another
Unidos te imaginas está preso en otro
country because the old man says so well that
país porque el viejito lo dice bueno que
Nicolás is a man with a good heart and
Nicolás es un hombre de buen corazón y
said that he is waiting for them to party in
dijo que los espera para que rumb en
Venezuela that is why the
Venezuela por eso los
migrants know that by returning to
migrantes saben que su regreso a
Venezuela they recover many things
Venezuela recuperan muchas cosas el
respect as human beings but also
respeto como seres humanos pero también
their right to come and party with their
su derecho a venir a rumbiar con su
family with their friends from the opposition
familia con sus panas desde la oposición
they will say Oh Trump is with Maduro In the end
dirán Ay Trump está con maduro Al final
everything ends up negotiating with the regime They did
todo termina negociando con el régimen
not say that the fight until the
No dijeron que que la lucha hasta el
end and now we see this brings ition
final y ahora vemos esto trae ición
you say Oh first Biden
ustedes digan Ay primero biden le
lifts the sanctions now Trump sends
levanta las sanciones ahora Trump manda
his emissaries I  I want to see the faces of
sus emisarios Yo quiero ver la cara de
the libertarians of my law, not that
los libertarios de mi ley no que tanto
the fata Donald Trump sucked so much,
le en chupó la fata Donald Trump a nos
the blonde wig betrayed us Trump is
traicionó el peluca rubia Trump está
negotiating with Nicola because Nicola the
negociando con nicolá porque Nicol el
best president in the world is not a groveling double
mejor presidente del mundo no es un
chin like the other one sells out the
papada arrastrado como el otro vende
country so they have and so they fine-tune
patria para que tengan y para que afinen
whoever messes with Venezuela dries up
el que se mete con Venezuela se seca
this situation has led
seco esta situación le ha llevado a
Michelo to assume that he has always been
michelo a asumir que siempre ha tenido
right about everything he has gone
la razón respecto a todo lo que ha ido
with commenting on the
con comentando sobre la relación de
United States' relationship with Venezuela I see that
Estados Unidos con Venezuela veo que
many are crying there Oh Trump How
muchos están llorando ahí Oh Trump Cómo
can he be negotiating with Maduro and I don't
puede estar negociando con maduro y no
know what else has hit you against the
sé qué más pum te ha chocado contra la
wall do you see have you realized that
pared viste te ha dado cuenta que no
what you believed does not coincide with
coincide lo que vos creías con la
reality and that is a product of when he
realidad y eso es producto de cuando te
fills your head with lies I
llena la cabeza de mentiras yo te
understand you friend I am not going to make fun of you
entiendo amigo no me voy a burlar fíjate
No more who warned you what was going to happen
No má quién te avisó lo que iba a pasar
Who always told you the truth And you know
Quién te dijo siempre la verdad Y sabes
what So you can see that they don't give a
qué Para que veas que no les importa un
damn about them they want
a ellos ellos quieren que
us to fight you they fill your
nosotros te hemos peleado te llena la
head with hate and hate brings
cabeza de odio y el odio trae
destruction  He brings falsehood with hate They
destrucción trae falsedad con odio te
made you donate money
hicieron que le dones plata Ya casi
Venezuela is almost here All these
Venezuela todos estos influencer
lying right-wing influencers Who do manage
mentirosos de derecha que sí manejan la
virality Manage the masses But look, they have
viralidad manejan la masividad pero mira
stolen your money And now they are going to
te han robado la plata y ahora te van a
deport you like an animal They are going to
deportar como un animal te van a
deport you, my friend You know what, you who
deportar amigo Sabes qué vos que te
left Venezuela I'm talking to you My
fuiste de Venezuela vos te hablo mi
grandfather had to emigrate from Spain because of a
abuelo tuvo que emigrar de España por un
blockade There was nothing to eat He was
bloqueo no había para comer estaba
malnourished On top of that My relatives had their
desnutrido encima a mis familiares le
lives taken by my grandfather
quitaron la vida de parte de mi abuelo
Because a fascist governed and
porque hay gobernado un fascista y
the country was blockaded mm I I know that
estaba bloqueado el país mm yo Yo sé que
in a blockade a country is ruined It
en un bloqueo un país se arruina se
melts That's why they do a blockade Because of the
funde por eso hacen un bloqueo por el
blockade you left They have filled your
bloqueo te fuiste Te han llenado la
head with from there so that you hate the government
cabeza de allá para que odie al gobierno
Your people Your country to everything and from there
a tu gente A tu país a todo y desde allá
Who won, the one who promised that he would
Quién ganó el que prometió que iba a
overthrow I don't know who doesn't want to
derrocar no sé a quién no quiera segita
just follow me And now who is going to receive you here
no más Y ahora quién te va a recibir acá
Who is going to receive you here With blockade and
Quién te va a recibir acá con bloqueo y
sanctions and this whole country rose up It's not
sanción y todo este país se levantó no
like when you left It's not like
está como cuando te fuiste no está como
when you left Aes they heard that
cuando te fuiste aes escucharon ese
clique  Michelo is referring to the issue
clique michelo hace referencia a un tema
of deportations from the United States and
de deportaciones de Estados Unidos y es
in recent days there was a move
que en los últimos días hubo una movida
in which Gustavo Petro, president of
en la que Gustavo Petro presidente de
Colombia, was made completely ridiculous for
Colombia quedó en completo ridículo por
trying to confront Trump. The
intentar encarar a Trump el gobierno de
United States government was sending
Estados Unidos enviaba para Colombia
some deported people to Colombia either for
algunas personas deportadas o bien por
illegal immigration or for other
inmigración ilegal o bien por otros
reasons and Petro tried to stand up for
motivos y Petro pretendía plantarse por
the human rights of those people
los derechos humanos de esas personas
by demanding that they be brought in on other
como exigiendo que lo trajesen en otros
planes. It's a tremendous ridiculousness. What
aviones o sea una ridiculez tremenda lo
we are saying is that Colombia is
que estamos planteando es que Colombia
not going to receive any handcuffed Colombian men or
no va a recibir ningún colombiano o
women because the migrant
colombiana esposada porque el migrante
is not a
no es ni ningún
criminal. They are already calling it the
delincuente ya le llaman el conflicto
shortest diplomatic conflict in history,
diplomático más corto de la historia
although it may also be the worst
aunque también puede ser el peor
ridicule of a president. It all started
ridículo de un presidente todo empezó
when the Colombian socialist Gustavo
cuando el socialista colombiano Gustavo
Petro rejected the entry of two
Petro rechazó la entrada de dos aviones
US military planes with
militares estadounidenses con
Colombian immigrants deported from the
inmigrantes colombianos deportados desde
United States through X. Petro did
Estados Unidos a través de X Petro hizo
what communists usually do,
lo que los comunistas suelen hacer
wrapping himself in the flag of humanism and
envolverse en la bandera del humanismo y
condemned the practice and said he was against
condenó la práctica y se dijo en contra
treating migrants as
de tratar a los migrantes como
criminals and that he would receive
criminales y que recibiría a los
deported migrants only on
migrantes deportados solo en aeronaves
civilian aircraft. But Trump, who is  short-fused
civiles pero Trump que es de mecha corta
responded through tru social and
respondió a través de tru social y le
listed the sanctions that he would
enlistó las sanciones a las que se
face for refusing to receive
enfrentaría por la negativa de recibir a
his own compatriots emergency tariffs
sus propios connacionales aranceles de
of 25% on
emergencia del 25% a productos
Colombian products travel ban and
colombianos prohibición de viaje y
immediate revocation of visas to
revocación inmediata de visas a los
government officials but to these
funcionarios del gobierno pero a estos
socialists who love to get tangled up in
socialistas que les encanta enredarse en
words to say nothing in a very
las palabras para no decir nada en un
long message through X that
larguísimo mensaje a través de X que
surely not even Trump read in a
seguramente ni Trump leyó en un tono
confrontational tone he told him that he did not
confrontativo le dijo que no le
care what he thought and even
importaba lo que pensara e incluso
wrote I do not shake hands with
escribió yo no estrecho mi mano con
white slavers
esclavistas blancos
tumid the Americas and humanity in the
túmido las américas y la humanidad al
end Petro was left with his tail between his
final Petro se quedó con la cola entre
legs accepting that migrants
las patas aceptando que los migrantes
arrive in military planes in which
lleguen en los aviones militares en los
Trump commands But yes
que mande Trump Pero eso sí
guaranteeing them decent conditions as
garantizándoles condiciones dignas como
citizens subject to rights and
ciudadanos sujetos de derechos y hasta
is even preparing the presidential plane
está preparando el avión presidencial
to repatriate Colombians who
para repatriar a los colombianos que
are subject to deportation the
sean objeto de deportación el gobierno
Colombian government reports that we have overcome
de Colombia informa que hemos superado
the impasse with the government of the United
el impase con el gobierno de los Estados
States We will continue to receive
Unidos Seguiremos recibiendo a los
Colombians who
colombianos y a las colombianas que
return under the condition of  deported
retornen en condición de deportados
guaranteeing them decent conditions
garantizándoles las condiciones dignas
as citizens subject to law the
como ciudadanos sujetos de derecho la
truth is that when I was watching
verdad es que yo cuando estuve viendo
this move I didn't understand too much the
esta movida No entendí demasiado la
attitude of Petro, I mean it was like playing the
actitud de Petro o sea fue como hacer el
clown For doing it no, he had no
payaso Por hacerlo no no tenía ningún
reason to do it
motivo para ello Siempre han existido
Deportations from the United States have always existed
las deportaciones desde Estados Unidos
when there is someone illegal or when
cuando hay alguien ilegal o cuando
they commit a crime or whatever,
comete algún delito o lo que sea
even with the Biden government in
inclusive con el gobierno de biden de
fact in the last few days they brought up
hecho en los últimos días le han sacado
this subject in an interview and it was
este tema en una entrevista y quedó
even worse if possible eh
todavía peor parado si cabe eh el año
last year there were 53,000 Colombians who
pasado fueron 53,000 colombianos los que
were repatriated in the same
fueron repatriados en las mismas
circumstances that did not change what
circunstancias eso no cambió lo que
we are proposing and the
nosotros estamos planteando y el
president of the republic emphasizes that
presidente de la república lo recalca es
Colombia is not going to receive any
que Colombia no va a recibir ningún
Colombian man or woman in handcuffs because
colombiano o colombiana esposada porque
the migrant is not a criminal but
el migrante no es un delincuente pero
sorry president It's that yesterday the
perdón presidente Es que ayer los
planes arrived anyway but that the
aviones llegaron igual pero av que el
president of Colombia knew But how can
presidente de Colombia supiera Pero cómo
the president of Colombia not know
no va a saber el presidente de Colombia
If that has been the case all the time
Si eso ha sido durante todo el tiempo
as you say 53000 how is it going to be and you
como dice 53000 cómo va a ser y usted
yourself recognize that there was a negotiation
mismo reconoce que había una negociación
how can you tell us that you did not know that  These
cómo nos puede decir que usted no sabía
were conditions that could be
que eran las condiciones que pueden ser
criticized but were used
criticables pero las que se utilizaban
as standard procedure by the United
como como procedimiento habitual por
States but that's how it is
parte de Estados Unidos pero es así
But anyway after all this
Pero bueno después de toda esta
information we now return to the topic of
información volvemos ahora al tema de
social justice fighters because I've already
los justicieros sociales que ya los he
missed them And it's that after everything we've
menos Y es que después de todo lo que
been commenting on in
hemos estado comentando en vídeos
previous videos that I recommend that you
anteriores que os recomiendo que os
take a little tour of the channel to
peguis una vueltecilla por el canal para
stay up to date with all the lords where among
estar al día de todoos lores donde entre
other things they were constantly on
otras cosas estuvieron constantemente en
their trip to Venezuela uploading videos
su viaje a Venezuela subiendo vídeos
like this the [ __ ] mother that
como este la madre que
loig where is Edmundo right now
loig dónde está Edmundo en este momento
Where is he [ __ ] himself A minute of
Dónde está se Un minuto de
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
silence that
silencio que
[Music]
[Música]
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
is now when they are back and they
está ahora cuando están de vuelta y
are seeing everything that has happened and what is being
están viendo todo lo que ha pasado y lo
said about them and that
que se está hablando de ellos y que
even Michelo they want to catch him
incluso a michelo lo quieren atrapar
to put him in jail I think that they are
para meter lo preso creo que están
possibly and maybe just possibly
posiblemente y tal vez solo posiblemente
a little scared so much so that in
un poquito asustados tanto es así que en
a radio program in which they just
un programa de radio en el que acaban de
participated they commented that they did not
participar han comentado que ellos no
do any type of activism and that they
hicieron ningún tipo de activismo y que
were simply there on a
simplemente pues estaban allí de visita
chill visit because they had been invited not
chill porque los habían invitado ni
even  is that we went to campaign I mean we didn't
siquiera es que fuimos a militar O sea
go because we were invited And if they
no fuimos porque nos invitaron Y si nos
invite us, what are we going to know
invitan tipo qu vamos a saber nosotros
who finances, like they invited us and as
quién financia tipo nos invitaron y como
communicators it seems important to us to go In
comunicadores nos pare importante ir De
fact, in the last few hours, Michelo
hecho en las últimas horas michelo
when they ask him where he earns money
cuando le preguntan de dónde gana Diner
What does it depend on, no, his salary has come out a
De qué depende no su sueldo ha salido un
bit by petenera commenting on what he earns
poco por petenera comentando lo que gana
with the YouTube shorts and then
con los shorts de YouTube y después el
Michelo's salary is a secret salary
sueldo de michelo es secreto sueldo
Well, my salary varies depending on the virality I
Bueno mi sueldo varía según la viralidad
have, I'll explain why For
que tenga yo te explico por qué Por
example, on my secondary channel,
ejemplo en mi canal secundario de
Michelo Picante, I have these videos that
michelo picante Tengo estos videos que
are the most viewed of the month, for example,
son los más vistos del mes por ejemplo
the first video, one of my sister's, which
el primer video uno de mi hermana que
well, generated 00 for me with 10 million
bueno me generó 00 con 10 millones de
views, it's 17 seconds of video, the
visitas son 17 segundos de video los
shorts have more views but less pay
shorts tienen más visit pero menos paga
because they are shorter, for example, it has
porque son más cortos por ejemplo tiene
35 million views, what's more, the
35 millones de visitas lo que sí que el
video lasts 30 seconds, which left me with
video dura 30 segundos lo cual me dejó
an income of 1,000 $100 and These are
un ingreso de 1000 $100 y Estos son
YouTube shorts, no, I mean, they are videos
shorts de YouTube no o sea son videos
that to this day continue to add
que hasta el día de hoy siguen sumando
views and income and you will say, Ah,
visitas e ingresos y ustedes dirán Ah
Michel, it is  millionaire Well friend not
Michel es millonario Bueno amigo no
all the videos I publish go
todos los videos que publico se hacen
viral the creators know it is a
virales los creadores lo saben es una
statistic I believe that the more
estadística yo creo que mientras más
videos one makes the more chance one has of
videos uno hace más chance tiene de
making it go viral The good thing is that
hacer que se haga viral Lo bueno que
when you hit a viral video it continues to
cuando pegas un video viral te sigue
generate income not as if it were an
generando ingresos no como si fuera un
asset that is why you see that many people talk
activo por eso ven que mucha gente habla
about me because it brings them visits and they also
de mí porque les trae visitas y también
monetize with me It is like on the
monetizan conmigo Es como que en
internet the content creator there are
internet el creador de contenido hay
people who do not have codes and do
gente que no tiene códigos y hace
anything to have visits
cualquier cosa con tal de tener visitas
Yes I make content by vocation which is
Sí hago un contenido por vocación que es
by ideology as you see Michelo
por ideología como ven ahí a michelo
explaining there where
explicando De dónde sale supuestamente
his money supposedly comes from yes maybe he has his
su dinero sí que a lo mejor él tiene sus
sources of income and he generates some
fuentes de ingreso Y genera algo de
money but to stay in
dinero pero para estar hospedado en
four star hotels eating in
hoteles cuatro estrellas comer en
restaurants the truth is that
restaurantes la verdad es que todo el
everyone also knows in advance that he is
mundo sabe también de antemano que está
paid by Nicolás Maduro and that he has a
pagado por Nicolás maduro y que tiene un
salary there you will
un salario ahí también recordaréis
also remember that in the last videos that we
también que en los últimos vídeos que
were making commenting on the subject of
estuvimos haciendo comentando el tema de
Michelo there is a legislator and lawyer
michelo hay un legislador y abogado
Yamil Santoro who is cornering him
yamil Santoro que anda acorralo
judicially and who is completely
judicialmente y que está completamente
determined to put him in Cana because this
decidido de meterlo en Cana pues este
man Yamil Santoro Does not stop
hombre yamil Santoro No para de
corner him not only
acorralarlo ya no solamente
judicially but he has also exposed his
judicialmente sino que le ha sacado los
dirty laundry And the thing is that Michelo, whom
trapitos sucios Y es que michelo al que
Maduro has been somewhat
maduro tiene últimamente un tanto
abandoned lately, as we were already commenting on
abandonado como Ya estuvimos comentando
in the previous videos, had a change
en los vídeos anteriores tuvo un cambio
of thinking that was too radical to
de pensamiento demasiado radical para
be credible, he influenced the prostitute of the
ser creíble influen prostituto de la
dictatorship of Nicolás Maduro, what you
dictadura de Nicolás maduro lo que
probably didn't know is that before
seguramente no sabían es que antes de
becoming the most communist of
convertirse en el más comunista de los
communists and the most pimp of
comunistas y en el más alcahuete de los
pimps, Michelo was a libertarian And he
alcahuetes michelo era libertario Y
said that Maduro was a dictator because being a
decía que maduro era un dictador por ser
libertarian doesn't mean that I have to
libertario no quiere decir que tengo que
be in favor of the United
estar a favor de estado
States negotiating with the
Estados Unidos negociando con el
dictator Nicolás
dictador Nicolás
Maduro, that's why Mich when we say that
Maduro por eso Mich cuando decimos que
you sold out to the regime it's because it's more
te vendiste al régimen es porque es más
than evident that no one goes from being a liberal
que evidente nadie pasa a ser liberal
libertarian to being a communist and defending
libertario a ser comunista y a defender
a dictatorship,
una dictadura
and not only that, the other day in one of
sal y no solo eso el otro día en uno de
the live broadcasts of a little angry guy, to whom we
los directos de tipito enojado a quien
send a huge kiss from here and
desde aquí le mandamos un beso enorme y
we hope to see him back here very soon, it was
esperamos verle muy pronto por aquí de
learned in Scoop of a new
vuelta se supo en Primicia de un nuevo
judicial proceeding against Michelo, the
trámite judicial en contra de michelo la
news  It was just sent by the FAD, which
noticia me la acaba de enviar el fad que
is the one filing the complaint, it is the
es quien presenta la denuncia es el F
Argentine Forum for the Defense of
Argentino por la defensa de la
Democracy. Michelo was reported a
Democracia michelo fue denunciado hace
few minutes ago. The complaint was made by
unos minutos la denuncia la realizaron
four national deputies and the
cuatro diputados nacionales y el
Minister of Security of the city of
ministro de seguridad de la ciudad de
Buenos Aires, who is also the president of the
Buenos Aires que a vez el presidente del
FAD, Waldo Wolf, the ministers Sonina
fad waldo Wolf los ministros sonina
Manfi, Fernando Iglesias, Sabrina Ahet, and
manfi Fernando Iglesias Sabrina ahet y
Maximiliano Ferrar, who are mainly filing the
Maximiliano ferrar los que presentan la
complaint. The reason is
denuncia principalmente y el motivo es
for covering up crimes against
por encubrimiento de delitos de lesa
humanity in Venezuela. That is the cause.
humanidad en Venezuela Esa es la causa
The complaint is very good. I don't know what
como está la denuncia muy bien No sé qué
you think. Surely many of you
pensáis ustedes seguramente muchos
will think that this is some kind of
pensaréis que esto es una especie de
propaganda, both Yamil not
propaganda ya tanto lo de yamil no
making content and now these people,
haciendo contenido como ahora esta gente
this group called the Argentine Forum for
este grupo llamado foro argentino para
the Defense of Democracy in which
la defensa de la democracia en la que
several deputies participate, but it
participan varios diputados pero sí que
is true that at least the complaint has been
es verdad que al menos la denuncia se ha
confirmed and whether he likes it or not, Michelo is going to have to
confirmado y quiera que no michelo va a
face all these
tener que hacer frente a todos estos
problems and defend himself. At the very least, he will have to
problemas y defenderse como mínimo
defend himself. From the FAD, we have decided to
defenderse desde el fad hemos decidido
denounce Diego Omar Suárez Arias,
denunciar a Diego Omar Suárez Arias
Michelo because his propaganda, contracted
michelo porque su propaganda contratada
by the Nicolás Maduro regime, is
por el régimen de Nicolás maduro tiene
intended to cover up crimes.
por objeto encubrir los delitos los
very serious crimes of inhumanity that are
gravísimos delitos de deshumanidad que
systematically committed in
se cometen de manera sistemática en
Venezuela to generate terror in the
Venezuela para generar terror en la
civilian population Michelo what he does
población civil michelo lo que hace
when he generates this type of propaganda
cuando genera este tipo de propagandas
is try to hide the crimes that are
es intentar ocultar los delitos que allí
committed there And try to generate
se cometen Y tratar con ello de generar
impunity for the perpetrators of these
impunidad en los autores de los
very serious crimes against humanity,
gravísimos crímenes de la humanidad
from FAD we are not going to allow this to
desde fad no vamos a permitir que esto
happen and we have already filed a
ocurra y ya hemos presentado una
criminal complaint for him to be investigated
denuncia penal para que se lo investigue
the other day Even the streamer
el otro día Incluso el streamer el
Chosas without saying his name but I and I
chocas sin decir su nombre pero yo y
think making a clear reference to
creo que haciendo una Clara referencia a
Michelo, who is the one he is
michelo que es de quien más está
talking about the most and who the entire planet is
hablando y a quien todo el planeta está
pointing out as an idiot, was
señalando por estuvo
commenting that it is completely
comentando que es completamente
impossible unless you are crazy that you
imposible a no ser que estés reventado
go
de la cabeza que vayas de forma
voluntarily to the dictatorship of Venezuela
voluntaria a la dictadura de Venezuela a
unless you are obviously under
no ser que estés evidentemente bajo
some interest, any person with a
algún interés cualquier persona con un
minimum of general culture knows that the
mínimo de cultura general sabe que la
solution is the complete opposite at maduro
solución es todo lo contrario a maduro
point, that's it, only the
punto ya está solo le van a defender la
people of the extreme left and the people of
gente de extrema izquierda y la gente de
this my mental left will defend him So we should not
este mi izquierda mental Así que no hay
take them into account I mean, it really
que tenerlos en cuenta O sea de verdad
is that simple you can't think that
es así de sencillo no puedes pensar eso
If you think  that's because you have
Si piensas eso es porque tienes
benefits because you have a benefit if you
beneficios porque tienes un beneficio si
have a benefit normal that you vote for them
tienes un beneficio normal que los votes
but it's because you have a
pero es porque tienes un interés
personal interest it's not because you believe in
personal no es porque creas en la
individual freedom or because you believe in
libertad individual ni porque creas en
equality no no You don't believe that you
en la igualdad no no Tú no crees eso tú
have a little envelope and you steal a little bit
tienes un sobrecito y trincas un poquito
then of course you are a Chavista that's why you
entonces claro eres chavista así sí que
are a Chavista By the way a few
eres chavista Por cierto hace unos
minutes ago we mentioned my colleague
minutos hemos mencionado a mi colega
angry guy or I would recommend his channel
tipito enojado o recomendaría su canal
if it weren't because I'm completely
si no fuera porque estoy completamente
sure that you already know him But well
seguro de que ya lo conoces Pero bueno
if not, angry guy and angry guy
si no es así tipito enojado y tipito
Live the other day we had him here on
Live el otro día lo tuvimos por aquí por
the channel and it was a complete pleasure I
el canal y fue un completo gustazo os
recommend that you watch the chat I
recomiendo que que veáis la charla que
had with him also if this topic continues to be
tuve con él también si este tema sigue
talked about I won't hesitate to invite him
dando que hablar no dudaré en invitarlo
again if he wants to come this will
de nuevo si él quiere venir esta va a
always be his home because the truth is
ser siempre su casa porque la verdad es
that we were super comfortable with him
que estuvimos super cómodos con él se
time flew by he's had a
nos pasó el tiempo volado ha tenido un
beef in the last few days with a
bifeo en los últimos días con una
journalist and lawyer named Julia
periodista y abogada llamada Julia
Mengolini who the chick had taken and
mengolini que la tipa había cogido y
had called for
había hecho un llamamiento a que la
people to hit him I mean for people to go
gente le pegue O sea a que la gente vaya
and hit him on the street  dude before I
y le pegue por la calle a tipito antes
start I want to make it clear that this
de empezar quiero aclararte de que esto
is illegal indeed this is illegal
es ilegal efectivamente esto es ilegal
guys I want to tell you that if anyone
chicos quiero de decirles que si alguien
sees any of the trolls of my
llega a ver alguno de los troll de mi
law like dude the black Almeida and all
ley como tipito el negro Almeida y todos
those virgins obsessed with me
esos vírgenes obsesionados conmigo le
give them a good snort from me and
dan una buena surra de mi parte y le
say This is from mengo plum with
dicen Esta es de parte de mengo plum con
this what I want to say is There is no
esto lo que quiero decir es No hay marco
theoretical framework or pacifist disquisitions that
teórico ni disquisiciones pacifistas que
can stop the anger of those of us who are
puedan detener la ira de quienes somos
permanently attacked sometimes you
atacados de manera permanente a veces
have to throw a good punch and that's it
hay que poner una buena trompada y listo
Alberto Fernández would say well This is
diría Alberto Fernández bueno Esto es
Blue Sky the Twitter for cowards she
Blue Sky el Twitter para cagones ella se
left Twitter because Twitter was
fue de Twitter porque Twitter era
violent towards Blue Sky and the ironic thing is that
violento a Blue Sky y lo irónico es que
now that she is on Blue Sky Twitter
ahora que ella está en Blue Sky Twitter
is less violent because in the end Look
es menos violento porque al final Mira
who was the violent one on the part of
quién era la violenta por parte de
dude she has stated that she will not take
tipito ha afirmado que no tomará medidas
legal action against this lady it
legales contra esta señora que me
surprises me that she is a lawyer But well that's
sorprende que sea abogada Pero bueno eso
what the internet says if the internet says it you have to
es lo que dice internet si lo dice
believe it but it is
internet hay que creerlo pero sí que es
true that he dedicated some words to her the
verdad que le dedicó unas palabras el
other day live that were
otro día en directo que estuvieron
sublime as always dude making
sublimes como siempre tipito haciéndole
a little reflection on this lady I
una pequeña reflexión a esta señora
want you  just understand this, it
quiero que entiendan nada más esto que
's important, I don't I've had
es importante yo no Yo hace 6 años que
a YouTube channel for 6 years now, legally I'm
tengo un canal YouTube legalmente me
very careful with what I say, I would never
cuido un montón en lo que digo no
order people to be killed or people to be beaten up,
mandaría a matar gente o a golpear gente
never under any circumstances, it seems
nunca bajo ningún concepto me parece un
crazy to me, it seems like a total hijab,
delirio me parece un hijap putz total
but this woman is playing around on the
pero esta mujer como está jugando en las
networks and she thinks it's crazy and all a joke, she does it, you
redes y le parece picho y tod una jodita
know why I don't order
lo hace sabes por qué no mando a matar
people to be killed or people to be beaten up or whatever
gente o a golpear gente o lo que sea
because I know that there's always a crazy person
porque sé que siempre hay un loco
listening to me It doesn't matter that there's always
escuchándome No importa que siempre hay
a person who is unbalanced enough to listen to you,
una persona que está lo suficientemente
so you have to understand, say No, the
entonces tien que entender decir No la
truth is that I'd better not do it No, no, for a
verdad que mejor no hago No no por una
legal reason, for a question of whether there
cuestión legal por una cuestión de que
could be real consequences because you
puede haber consecuencias reales porque
already know I know that there are people who listen to me
ya s Ya sé que hay gente que me escucha
And follow me and take what I say as the
Y me sigue y toma lo que digo como una
truth Then they listen to me But well, that's how
verdad Entonces me hace caso Pero bueno
the W movement is sometimes, I don't
así es el movimiento W algunas veces no
know how you see it, for now I'm
sé ustedes cómo lo veis yo de momento
going to leave This video here, I
voy a ir dejando Este vídeo por aquí que
think that for today it's enough That said, I'll
creo que por hoy es suficiente Eso sí
be happy to read you in the
estaré encantado de leeros en la caja de
comments box, let me know if you want more
comentarios hacerme saber si queréis más
videos on this subject, you are  The
vídeos sobre este tema ustedes sois Los
Owners of the Channel So in the end I am
Dueños del Canal Así que al final yo soy
yours your submissive your lackey I don't
vuestro vuestro sumiso vuestro lacayo no
know that has come out a little strange but oh
sé eso ha quedado un poco raro pero
well I'll listen to you okay whatever
bueno yo os hago caso vale lo que
you ask me here You're going to I hope to be
ustedes me pidáis aquí lo Vais a Espero
able to upload this week also the
poder subir esta semana también el blog
New York blog that is pending and the
de Nueva York que está pendiente y el
rewind we are going to relaunch the rewind with
rewind vamos a reestrenar el rewind con
a little bit of reform okay with a little bit
un poquito de reforma vale con un poco
of arrangement So stay tuned to
de arreglo Así que estaros pendientes
the Channel activate the bell follow me
del Canal activar la campanita seguirme
also on Twitter Instagram and all
también en Twitter Instagram y todas
these little things I send you a big hug
estas cosillas os mando un abrazo muy
and until the next video bye
fuerte y hasta el siguiente vídeo chao
[Music]
[Música]